import { flashcardImg, examImg, learnImg } from "../utils"

export const flashCardsTest = [
    {
      front : "jabłko",
      back : "apple",
    },
    {
      front : "auto",
      back : "car",
    },
    {
      front : "rozumieć",
      back : "understanding",
    },
    {
      front : "szybki",
      back : "fast",
    },
    {
      front : "zachowanie",
      back : "behaviour",
      
    },
    {
      front : "wystawa",
      back : "exhibition",
      
    },
    {
      front : "muzyka",
      back : "music",
    },
    {
      front : "wysokość",
      back : "altitude",
    },
    {
      front : "maska",
      back : "mask",
    },
    {
      front : "rakieta",
      back : "rocket",
    },
    {
      front : "ubrania",
      back : "clothes",
    },
    {
      front : "testowanie",
      back : "testing",
    },
  ]

export const footerItems = [
  {
    text : "Regulamin",
    link : "/regulamin"
  },
  {
    text : "Polityka prywatności",
    link : "/private-policy"
  },
  {
    text : "O nas",
    link : "/about-us"
  },
]

export const panelBox = [
  {
    text : "Fiszki",
    link : "/decks",
    img : flashcardImg
  },
  {
    text : "Ucz się",
    link : "/learn",
    img : examImg
  },
  {
    text : "Test",
    link : "/tests",
    img : learnImg
  },
]